这个优德鸡的项目简直就是... (一鸡肉快餐连锁店)
The whole Chick-fil-A narrative is just...
如果可以说的话 先生
I mean, if I may, sir, it's...
那就是饮食界的奇葩啊 我说真的
It's food-nomenal. Really. It really is.
现在外面施工成这样
With that construction outside, man,
搞得我刚才在路上堵了整整两个小时
I was stuck in traffic for two hours.
我的膀胱都要憋爆了
My bladder was like a fuckin' blimp.
你应该多和食品制造商聊聊
You should maybe talk some more to the food manufacturing guys
还有健康顾问们 好的
And The health advisors. - Yeah.
来吧 女士 小聊一下就行了
Come on, ma'am, just some small talk.
不行的话微聊也可以
Even tiny talk will do.
好的 我懂 我会去的
Yeah, I know. I'm gonna do it.
天哪 这一早上就白瞎了啊
God, what a waste of a morning.
要是想对我逼供的话  根本就不用上什么老虎凳辣椒水
If you ever want me to confess, don't rip out my fingernails,
让我吃他妈一星期的素我就全招了
just make me eat like a vegan for a fuckin' week.
副总统看起来脸色跟吸血鬼似的
The VP look like she's about ready to open up a vein.
你没事吧?
You okay?
你看起来好像有点敷衍的意思 你知道吗? Amy
- You seem to be phoning it in a little. - You know what, Amy?
我从来就不想当副总统
I'm the veep I never wanted to be.
我得跟这帮二货说吃沙拉和体重指数
I'm talking salad wraps and body mass index to these idiots.
你真的该去了...
You should really just go and...
是的 我知道 感觉我的灵魂已经从下面拉出去了
Yeah, I know, feel my soul slide out of my ass.
好了 这个你拿着
All right, here. You take that.
我现在来积蓄能量了
I'm building up the energy right now.
这个闻起来跟出租车似的
This smells like the inside of a taxi cab.
同志们好啊 首长好
- Hi, guys. Hello. - Hello.
不用等太久了
Not too much longer.
一会我们照了集体照你们就可以走了
We'll get the group shot taken and then you guys can get moving.
太好了
Awesome!
这一早上效率真高!
What a productive morning.
你们觉得这里有东西能放到你们店里卖的么?
Can you envision selling some of these items
当然了 是的 也许色拉卷吧
at any of your stores, you think?
就是 色拉卷 葡萄  葡萄永远都不错
- Oh, sure. - Yeah. Wraps maybe.
葡萄...葡萄战无不胜啊
- Yeah, wraps. - Grapes. I mean, grapes are always good.
那些黄色的东西看起来...很...
Grapes are... hey, you can't beat grapes.
我告诉你们这些都是本地产的 而且都是有机食品 噢 哇
Those yellow things look... so...
更确切的说是有劲食品 噢
Well, I'll tell you it's all local
你吃的是啥我也要
- and it's all organic. - Oh, wow.
你那个东西没有变焦的么? 噢 Ken 你知道吗?
- Orgasmic's more like it, right? - Oh.
我们现在这里不拍照 好吗?
I'll have some of what you're having.
对不起 不 没关系的
- Do you have a zoom on that thing? - Oh, Ken, you know what?
你今晚回华盛顿么 Gary?
You back to DC tonight, Gary?
是的 我要早点回去
Yeah, I'm leaving a little bit earlier.
我爸今天过生日 不错
my dad is having his birthday dinner. - Nice.
不 他非常不尊重我的工作
He has very little respect for my job.
实际上他更希望我在这里工作
He actually much rather me work here.
搞伙食承包么? 不 在棒球场工作
- In catering? - No, a baseball stadium.
Oh.
做男人中的男人 运动员
A man's man, a jock.
是那些家伙中的一位
Rarrrh! One of those guys.
哇 那很难吧 谁说不是呢
- Wow, that's gotta be tough. - Yeah, tell me about it.
我是说对他而言很难
I meant for him.
苍天啊 你知道吗 Ken?
- Jesus. - Okay, you know what, Ken?
不能这么近 好吗? 好的
- Not so close, okay? - Okay.
谁也不用知道我哪边眉毛需要修了
Nobody needs to know which of my eyebrow hairs needs to be plucked.
对不起
Sorry.
集体照的事情怎么样了?
All right. What's going on with this group shot?
为什么耽搁了? 不会太久了 女士
- What's the delay? - It's not much longer, ma'am.
保持微笑
Just keep smiling.
把你皱上去的眉毛...
Turn that frown...
放下来哈
upside-down.
好的 好的
Okay. - Okay.
你看见他老摸我了没?
Do you see that he keeps touching me?
是的 我注意到了 而且他的手好小啊
- Yeah, I've noticed. - And his hands are really small.
他那敏感的小辣手啊~~
It's his feely, little, touchy, hot hands.
得有人告诉他他是为白宫工作的
Someone needs to tell him that he's working
不是后宫 (Penthouse 著名成人杂志)
with the White House and not Penthouse.
能借一步说话吗?
Hey, can I talk to you privately just for a second?
好的
Okay.
你们和甜甜脆搞的这个项目简直就是...
The whole thing that you guys have done with Krispy Kreme is just...
如果可以说的话 那就是饮食界的奇葩啊 真的
if I may, it's food-nomenal, really.
你知道我和Ted在交往 对吧?
So you know that I've been seeing Ted, right?
嗯哼 不久之前
- Mm-hmm. - A while ago,
我们喝了不少酒 又听了Springsteen的歌
a lot of wine was drunk and Springsteen was listened to
事情有点小失控...
and things got a little bit out of hand.
你们去偷车了?
You stole a car?
我们滚床单的时候没有用套子
We had unprotected sex,
而且我觉得我怀孕了
and I think I might be pregnant.
Oh...
这是有可能的 Amy
It's a possibility, Amy.
我还没有到更年期
I haven't reached menopause yet, you know.
我也不是不孕不育啥的 我知道这个可能性不大
I'm not barren. I know it's unlikely.
说不定我和30个男的
I could probably have unprotected sex with 30 men,
不要套子轮流来也不会出事
one right after the other, and it would be totally fine.
我的意思是 不 不会出大事
I mean, no, it wouldn't be totally fine.
我是说 这个绝对是出大事了
I mean, that would be a horrible thing.
我不是在怀疑你怀孕的能力 女士
I'm not doubting your fertility, ma'am,
但是一个未婚妈妈
but an unwed mother
不就是总统身边的定时炸弹?
one aneurism away from the presidency?
你觉得这个会是什么效果?
How do you think that plays?
这个包包有一个大格可以放东西
The bag has got one big storage area
还有60个小格子分布在各处
and then there are 60 separate pockets within the area.
- Hmm. - Wow!
看吧? 那可是不少要记的东西 Gary
- Right? - That is a lot to remember, Gary.
就是 就是
I know, I know.
但是你连看都不看就知道?
But can you do it without looking?
你来考我
Try me.
眼药水
Eye drops.
Ooh!
湿巾 有香的还是无香的?
- Wipes. - Scented, unscented?
有香的
Scented.
- Bam! - Wow!
太牛了... 真难以置信
- Knock it... - That's unbelievable.
希望我没有怀孕 否则的话
I hope I'm not pregnant, because, fuck, if I am,
我就完了 你知道吗?
I'm just finished, you know?
女士 我们行动起来!
- Ma'am. - Let's get moving!
你知道不能跟别人说吧? 我知道
- You know you'll have to keep it. - I know.
除非我们去墨西哥渡个特别假期啥的...
Unless we go on some sort of special vacation to Mexico and...
然后把医生弄死在沙漠里
kill the doctor in the desert.
父亲知道吗?
Father know?
什么 你不是玩我吧? 我才15岁么?
What, are you kidding me? What am I, 15?
我的意思是Ted 我去!不 不知道
- I mean Ted. - Oh, shit. No.
那一头我还在努力
No. I'm still working on that one.
你的相机是什么的? 这是部5D(市价1-2万rmb)
- What are you shooting with? - This is a 5D.
不是1D么?(市价5万左右) 不是
- Not a 1D? - No.
我拍这个用不着1D
Why would I need a 1D to shoot this?
我有一部1D
I have a 1D.
那个更贵 但是确实是好相机
It's more expensive, but it's a really nice camera.
你拍很多体育活动么? 连续的运动?
You shoot a lot of sports? Moving action?
还是拍很多水鸟抓鱼的照片?
You take hundreds of pictures of herons catching fish?
否则的话你就用不着1D
Because otherwise you don't need a 1D.
是的 但是我有一部1D
Right, but I have a 1D.
是
Yeah.
呃 你能帮我个忙么?
Hey, will you do me a favor?
你能帮我买杯真正的咖啡
Can you get me a real coffee
来代替他们这儿上的淘米水么?
instead of this fucking beige paint they're serving, okay?
中杯脱脂双倍拿铁加肉桂么?
Grande skinny latte, extra shot, and a dash of cinnamon?
是的
Yeah.
能给我带一个...? 我们接下来要做的是...
- Can I get some of the...? - This is what we're gonna do...
和营养学家拍照 和选手们聊一聊
Photos with the nutritionists, hang with the players,
去学校转一圈 然后就验孕
over to the school, then we pregnancy test you to fuck.
听着 能请你在去学校的路上买验孕棒么?
Listen, will you get the tests on the way to the school, please?
当然了 我马上就去
Absolutely. I'm heading there right now.
这个事显然只是你知我知哈
Obviously this is in our little circle of two.
显然是的 是的
Obviously. - Yeah.
嘿 Jonah
Hey, Jonah.
你屁眼里的天气怎么样了?
How's the weather up there in your asshole?
哈哈
Oh ho.
这个真有爱 Mike 你怎么样?
That's cute, Mike. How's it going?
很好 很好 正在温习媒体简报会的提纲
Good, good. Just going over my notes for the press briefing.
你收到本地倡议企业名单了么?
Hey, did you get those local business initiatives
我从总统那发过来的
I sent over from the president?
嗯哼 嗯哼 正在看呢
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm. Looking at them right now.
谢谢 这很有用 那就好
- Thank you. They're very helpful. - Oh, good.
我很高兴你在着手了 我能看见你 Mike
I'm glad you're right on top of that. I can see you, Mike.
什么? 噢 哈哈
What? Oh.
这太赞了! 你知道吗 Mike?
- This is awesome! - You know what, Mike?
总有一天你醒过来的时候 会发现
One day you're gonna wake up and you're gonna find
你的肺变成了烤点心
your lungs have turned to pastry.
我挂了 Jonah 有人打进来了
Gotta go, Jonah. Got incoming.
Mike Amy 什么事?
- Mike. - Amy, what's up?
Selina可能怀孕了 我们怎么办?
Selina might be pregnant. What do we wanna do?
这是真的么?
Is this for real?
如果是真的话 那对她来说
'Cause if it is, the best thing for her legacy
最好的结局就是在显肚子之前被刺杀了
is if she's assassinated before she starts showing.
不是完全确定
It's not definite.
还得测试一下才知道
She still needs to take some tests.
好吧 那我猜我应该在媒体发布会上加上这一条
Okay. I'll guess I'll just add this to the press release.
大家就可以开始下注了
People can start taking bets.
你知道这个事得暗箱操作
You know that this needs to be way under the lid.
再见 没事吧?
Bye. - All good?
必须的
Absolutely.
这可要乐坏一群7岁小朋友了
It's gonna knock the socks off of some seven-year-olds.
老爸 老爸 我喜欢啤酒
Dad, dad, I like beer.
那是因为我开啤酒的时候把嘴唇划伤了
That was because I cut my lip trying to open the bottle.
我就是不能照你的方法打开它
I just can't open it the way you do.
听着 副总统和我要和金莺队的队员
Listen, the veep and I are gonna have our photo taken
合照了
with the Orioles players.
Huh?
是的 我可以给你洗一张
Yeah, I can get you one.
靠 是的 靠 是的
Shit, yeah. Shit, yeah.
咖啡店他娘的在哪?
Where the fuck is coffee?
那在体育场的这一天
So that whole stadium day
对你来说就是拉关系群P吧? 那是
- was like a networking orgy for you, right? - Oh, yeah.
绝对的名片群射
Yeah, yeah. Business card bukkake.
你也应该在这里买点东西的...
You know, you should get something while we're here...
刮胡刀啊 止痛药什么的
Razor blades, a large amount of pain killers.
我勒个大…
Holy sh...
你怀孕了?
Are you pregnant?
Amy 不是吧 事业大忌啊 这就跟入了科邪教
Amy, come on, career-wise, that's like joining scientology
或者在脖子上刺青是一样的啊
or getting a fucking neck tattoo.
谢谢你的支持
Thanks for the support.
那你会需要休产假
So I guess you're gonna be needing maternity leave.
我就会是你当然的替代者
I'd be the obvious choice for your replacement.
这还真的是你第一想法唉
That is literally your first thought?
不 我的第一想法是 你的身材就完蛋了
No. My first thought was, there goes your figure,
不过我没有说 因为我觉得那个会惹你生气的
but I didn't say that because I thought it would be upsetting.
谢谢 你知道吗 如果是男孩的话
Thanks. You know, if it's a boy,
我也许会给他取你的名 然后管他叫小人
maybe I'll name him after you. Call him fuck weasel.
Ken 我应该在这里吗?
Ken, is this where I should be?
不要太挤了 是的 不要太挤了
- Don't be too clustered. - Yeah, don't be too clustered.
谢谢 我来就行
Thank you. I got it.
如果你能稍微移到...
So if you could just move a little bit...
是的 移一点 这样大家不是都挤在一边 这样大家不是都挤在一边 都太靠那边了
- Yeah, a little bit so we're not all on one side. - So we're not on one side.
你能照到所有人么? 谢谢 我想他们听见我的话了
Can you See everybody? - I think they heard me.
好了 大家再说一遍我们行动起来!
Yes, how about one where we say let's get moving?
我们行动起来!
Let's get moving!
好了 再来一次怎么样?
All right, how about another one?
这一张我们说牛油果真美!
Another where we say awesome avocado!
牛油果真美! 好的 非常好
- Awesome avocado! - Yes, that was great.
好了 谢谢你们的耐心
All right! Thank you for your patience.
非常感谢你们能来 女士
- Thank you so much for being here. - Ma'am.
这肯定...怎么了? 先生们
It sure... Yes? Yes? - Gentlemen.
施工挖到了一根主要天然气管道
Construction hit a gas main.
发生了严重泄漏 在安全清理之前大家都必须呆在这里
There's a serious leak. Everybody must stay in here until it's made safe.
对不起
Sorry.
鉴于危险 我们需要每个人 都呆在这个房间内
Because of the danger, we need everybody to stay in the room.
我们会通报情况的
We'll update you.
听着 呃 但是我可以走 对吧?
Listen, uh, but I can get out of here, right?
大概一个小时以后吧
Probably in about an hour.
一个小时? 是的 女士
- An hour? - Yes, ma'am.
对副总统的到访
We're so excited about
我们感到非常激动 我们也很激动
- the vice president's visit. - Oh, we're very excited, too.
Amy是真心怀里揣着个娃一样激动
Amy's practically having a baby about it.
对吧? 呃 孩子们在等了
- Isn't that right? - Well, the children are waiting.
这边请
Right this way.
小朋友们 下午好 下午好
Hey, kids. Good afternoon.
我叫Dan 这是Amy
My name is Dan, this is Amy.
我们为副总统工作
And we work for the vice president
美利坚合众国的
of the United States of America.
很酷对吧?
- Yay. - Pretty cool, right? Yeah.
好的 好孩子说吧
Yeah, my man right here.
我爸爸在国务院工作
My dad works in the state department.
真的吗? 什么职位?
Really? What position?
贸易政策主管 那他认识Roger Aldrige咯?
Trade policy executive. - So he knows Roger Aldrige?
呃 我不知道
Uh, I don't know.
你是在和八岁的孩子攀关系么?
Are you networking with an eight-year-old?
是的
Yeah.
那...
So...
等一下 哥们
Hold on one second, chief.
有问题吗? 有天然气泄漏
- Problem? - There's a gas main leak.
Selina至少要迟到一个钟头
Selina's gonna be delayed at least an hour.
要是让孩子们等那么久的话他们会发疯的
These kids are gonna go berserk if they have to wait that long.
我们得哄着他们
We have to keep them entertained.
放点狮子王DVD 然后来两片利他林 (常用于治疗小儿多动症)
Lion King DVD and two shots of ritalin.
你可真是个好爹 我就是这么长大的
- You'll be such a great dad. - That's how I was raised.
好了我们开始吧?
All right, shall we, gentlemen?
Sean 要不我们还是趁你没有出现断酒谵妄
Sean, why don't we start with your question
还能写字的时候由你先开始问吧?
before you get the DTs and you can't write in your notebook.
你能说一下健康倡议的情况么?
Can you brief on the new health initiative?
是你上海报宣传么 Mikey?
Are you its poster boy, Mikey?
不过这真是个好问题
Actually, though, great question.
我们在巡回竞选的时候
You know, we were on the campaign trail
看见一个女人带着很胖的儿子
and we saw a woman with a very large boy.
副总统转过来对我说
And the vice president turned to me and said,
我要从肥胖症的监狱里把那个男孩解救出来
I'd like to free that boy from the prison of obesity.
还有别人有问题么?
Anybody else?
Leon West 华盛顿邮报的
Leon West, Washington Post.
有线人告诉我副总统
A source tells me that the VP shit-canned
因为有特勤人员冲她笑就炒了他
a secret service agent just for smiling at her.
你能回答我是或不是么?
Can you give me a yes or no on that, please?
我相信他是因为用的古龙水才被调走的
I believe he was reassigned because of his cologne.
他用的是Paco Rabanne
It was Paco Rabanne.
这又不是80年代了 对吧?
I mean, this is not the '80s anymore, right?
没有人用了 也许Sean会
Nobody wears that stuff. Sean might.
不过你可能更愿意直接喝 对吧 Sean?
You'd probably rather drink it, though. Right, Sean?
那必须的 谢谢 是的
That's necessary. Thank you, yes.
我看见过 我是酒鬼
- I've seen you. - I'm a drunk.
好了 你个废物点心
Okay, every which way but douche,
我要你现在回答我的问题
I want you to answer my question now.
我相信你问的是无聊的问题 Leon
I believe, ahem, you asked a boring question, Leon,
所以我才给了你一个无聊的答案
and I gave a boring answer.
这就像碳补偿一样
That's like carbon offsetting.
Mike 我不会笑的 你可能会丢掉饭碗的
Mike, I wouldn't be smiling. You might lose your job.
你懂我意思吗?
You understand my point?
你不觉得Selina Meyer就为了微笑
You don't find it repugnant that Selina Meyer
炒掉一位特勤人员很讨厌么?(与怀孕音近)
let a secret service agent go for smiling?
讨厌? 是的
Repugnant? - Yes.
是说副总统讨厌么?
You're calling the vice president repugnant?
这个说法很情绪化 先生
That's a very emotive term, sir,
而且还有点神经 我要说
and a little prissy, I might add.
我19岁的时候曾经在监狱里呆过一晚
I spent a night in jail when I was 19 once.
那都比这个有意思
That was more fun than this.
如果我们在这儿还得多呆一分钟
Well, if we get trapped here another minute,
我就要杀了你吃肉
I'm gonna kill you and eat you,
因为我不能再吃他妈的沙拉三明治了
because I will not eat another fuckin' falafel.
他妈的Jimmy Olsen (超人的好朋友摄影记者)
Hey, Jimmy fuckin' Olsen,
你最好是在我爆你菊
get lost before I shove that thing up your ass
让你另一个眼红起来之前消失
and give you another kind of red eye to worry about.
好的
Okay.
外面那两个人怎么了?
What is going on out there with those two?
你知道吗? 知道 他们气坏了
- Do you know? - Yeah, he's all pissed off.
他们整天都在抱怨这场活动和吃的
They've been complaining all day about the event and the food.
噢 我走动的时候听见的
Oh. - I overhear stuff as I move around.
而且我会读唇语
Plus, I can lip-read.
你会读唇语? 是的
you Can lip-read? - Yeah.
是的 我可以看出来你在说什么
Yes, I can tell what are you saying now.
你读出来我之前
Could you lip-read earlier
对Amy说你的事了么?
when I was talking about you to Amy?
没有 那太糟了 说的全是好话啊
- No. - Oh, that's too bad. It was all good.
谢谢 当然了
- Thank you. - Oh, sure.
Amy.
天哪 好多鼻涕啊
God, that is a lot of snot.
嘿 能把笔还给我吗?
Hey, can I have my pen back?
Mike 你好 谢谢
Mike, hi. Thank you.
我只是想警告你 最重要的事...是微笑故事
I just wanna warn you, on top of everything else... smile story.
能把笔帽也还给我吗? 这个还有个笔帽的
Can I get the pen cap, too? This came with a pen cap.
你那边到底在搞什么鬼? 你在听吗?
What the hell is going on over there? Are you listening?
是的 是的 故事 什么...?
Yes, yes. Story. What...?
笔帽 笔帽在哪?...在你嘴里吗?
The pen cap. Where was the pen... in your mouth?
你放到嘴里了吗?
Did you put it in your mouth?
我只是想给你提个醒 好吧?
Okay, I just wanna give you a heads-up, all right?
已经传出去了 他们说她害了病
It's out there. They're saying she's repugnant.
噢 天哪
Oh, my God.
嗨 我刚和Mike通了电话
Hi. - I have just had a phone call from Mike.
他说媒体说你怀了孕
He said that the press is saying you are pregnant.
他说消息已经传出去了
He's saying it's out.
不 不可能啊
No, it can't be.
你说什么呢? 没人知道啊
What are you talking about? Nobody knows.
他说Leon West说你怀孕了
He said that Leon West said that you're pregnant.
我勒个大去!
Holy f... uck.
呃 我不能动嘴唇
Ugh, I can't move my lips.
好了 我挂了 Gary正在往我这儿打
Okay, I'm going because Gary's calling.
别告诉Gary
Don't tell Gary.
不 Amy 他们不让我进去
No, Amy, they're not gonna let me through.
我快没时间了
I'm running out of time here.
我爸要一张照片
My dad needs a picture.
好了 我要你
Okay, I need you
去给副总统买验孕棒
to get a pregnancy test for the veep.
噢 我...我...我滴苍天啊!
Oh, my... oh, my God.
好兴奋哦 不 不 嘘
- That's kind of exciting. - No, no. Shh, shh.
我可以绑个婴儿背带什么的带着宝宝到处跑
I can carry the baby around in a little sling or something like that.
噢 我...等等 这算是坏消息 因为她还没结婚 对不对
Oh, my... oh, wait, this is bad because she's not married, right?
没错 所以要严格确认
Indeed, and this is strictly need-to-know.
我要买哪种验孕棒 是不是有很多种类啊
What kind of test do I get? Are there different kinds of tests?
我要怎么解释 我买什么
Like, how do I break it down? What do I get?
我手上就一种 所以你能找多少是多少
I've only got one, so you need to get as many as you can find, okay?
我们要确切结果 知道吗
We need to be sure, okay?
我们要速度搞定这事 好
We need to shock-And-awe this thing. - Okay.
嘿 宝宝有什么情况
Hey. So what's the intel on the baby?
情况
Intel.
知道 权限被否了
Copy that. Security clearance denied.
难道孩子爹是Jonah
Is Jonah the dad?
所以你才一脸 喝了瓶drano的样子?(沟渠去污剂品牌)
Is that why you look like you wanna drink a bottle of drano?
我不是怪你 只是分娩过程会很久
I don't blame you. That's gonna be a long labor.
人家要轮班才能把孩子从你体内拔出来
They're gonna be pulling that kid out of you in shifts.
Jonah 在 女士
- Jonah? - Yes, ma'am.
我们要摆脱这种坐牢的感觉
We gotta get rid of this whole prison-yard-vibe feeling.
得做点什么
We gotta do something.
虽然我们必须呆在体育场内
Well, we have to stay within the stadium,
但还是可以邀请他们下去 跟金莺队的球员碰个面
but we could invite the guys down to meet the Orioles players.
行 我们就这么做
Okay, that's exactly what we gonna do.
我不记得去查那些球员的资料了
I forgot to find out something about the players.
我不知道要对他们说什么 我可以帮你
- I don't know what to say to them. - I can help you along.
噢 你懂棒球么 我懂啊
- Oh, you know about baseball? - I do, yeah.
你可以做我的Gary吗 可以
- You can be my Gary? - Yeah, yeah.
我是成人版Gary 好
- I'll be the adult version of Gary. - Okay.
Jonah 看得见我吗
Jonah, can you see me?
呃 看见 告诉我号码
Uh, yeah. Give me their numbers.
我给你解释 等等 我看
- I'll go off that. - Hold on. Let me see.
Jake Arrieta 他是个开局投手
Jake Arrieta. He's a starting pitcher.
他左边的39号 Tommy Hunter
On his left is number 39, Tommy Hunter.
是个开局投手
He's a starting pitcher.
等等 他是开局投手? 对
- Wait, he's the starting pitcher? - Yes.
再旁边一位先生...是Jim Palmer
The next gentleman... Oh, that's Jim Palmer.
他进了名人堂 传奇来的
He's a hall-of-famer. That guy's a legend.
他也是个开局投手
He's a starting pitcher as well.
你不要老说开局投手
You don't have multiple starting pitchers.
这儿只有一个投手板
There's one pitcher's mound.
你看见的是一个还是三个
You see one mound or three mounds?
我看见一个 棒球比赛本来就只一个投手板
- I see one mound. - That's how you play baseball.
他们不是在同一天投的
They don't pitch on the same day.
你都搞不清自己在说什么
You don't have any idea what you're talking about.
真他妈蠢
Fuckin' idiot.
你好 嗨
Hello! Hi!
很荣幸见到您 女士 你是Jake吧
- Honor to meet you, ma'am. - And you are Jake.
对的 女士 噢 真好
- Yes, ma'am. - Oh, how nice.
你是开局投手 其中一个 是的 女士
- And you're the starting pitcher. - One of them. Yes, ma'am.
好 很好
Okay. Wonderful.
那你就是Tommy了 我是 我是
So you must be Tommy. - I am. I am.
呃 你是开局投手吗
Um, are you a starting pitcher?
我是 我是 你是开局...嗯
- I am, I am, I am. - You are a starting... ahem.
喂 老爸 我还在体育场
Hello, dad. I'm still at the stadium.
对 对
Yeah, yeah.
我跟队伍...我们家队员在一起
I'm with the team... my playas.
我会帮你搞到相片的
I will get you that pic, man.
各种强大(80年代灌篮术语)
Boom shaka laka.
他们就是这么讲话的
That's how they talk.
好
Okay.
这些是你们这儿所有验孕棒了吧
Are these all the pregnancy tests you have?
你应该是拿完了 好
I think you got them all. - Okay.
希望你能得到想要的结果
I hope you get the result you're looking for.
不是我要用
No, it's not for me.
是我姐姐 什么
- It's my sister. - I'm sorry?
我...你刚看到没
I... did you see that?
看什么 没事
See what?
我...
Okay, um, I just...
我还要不要帮姐姐买点其他东西
Is there any other stuff I should get for my sister?
比如孕妇内衣?
Like, um... maternity underwear?
她怀多久了 天 我不知道
- How long has she been pregnant? - Oh, God, I don't know.
她的私生活我完全不了解
I don't know anything about her private life.
只知道她前几周好忙好忙的
I do know, however, that the past few weeks she has been pretty busy.
我不建议买孕妇内衣 好的 好吧
I'd hold off on the maternity underwear.
这几个字跟这...这上衣搭配 真是绝了
Isn't this nice how the lettering works on these... on these tops?
谢谢
Thank you.
噢 天 我要...知道吗
Oh, brother. I'm just... you know what?
财政部长来电话了
I've got the treasury secretary calling.
我先接了 马上回来
Let me take this and I'm gonna be right back.
我很抱歉 失陪
I'm so sorry. Pardon me.
喂 喂 Ted
Hello? Hello, Ted?
嘿 下午要不要来个欢乐一刻?
Hey. So are you looking for a little afternoon delight?
不要 先听我说 我要告诉你件事
No. Listen to me for a second. I gotta tell you something.
我可能怀孕了 知道吧
I might be pregnant. All right?
对不起了 我只能直说
I'm sorry to have to be so blunt about it,
时间不够
but I don't have a lot of time.
各位 能给我五分钟私人时间吗
Um, guys, can I have five minutes?
什么 等一下
- What? - One second, please.
你还在吗 这不可能
- Are you still there? - That's impossible.
怎么会不可能 姐还没那么老
No, it's not impossible. I'm not that old.
我的天呐 好了 你缓过来没
- Oh, my God. - All right, you over that bombshell?
因为这个消息后面
Because that bombshell just gave birth
还藏了个更重口味的
to a bigger bombshell.
媒体知道了
The press know about this.
妈的 我知道
- Oh, fuck. - I know.
所以我们只能这样了 知道吧
So this is what we're gonna do, all right?
我们结婚
We're getting married.
计划就是
And the plan is
我们已经订婚了 就是六周前
that we got engaged, like, six weeks ago
或者之类的 清楚吧
or something, all right?
你求婚了 给了我一戒指
You proposed by giving me some sort of a ring
放在他妈心形牡蛎之类的东西里面
in a heart-shaped, fuckin' oyster thing or something.
不过 细节才是关键 Ted
You know, the key is in the details, though, Ted.
知道没 知道
Okay? - Okay.
不管怎样 你先去买个戒指
Anyway, listen, you've gotta get me a ring.
现在就去买
You've gotta go, you've gotta get a ring now.
得是大钻的
And it's gonna have to be a big one.
那 你手指围多大
Well, what size is your finger?
老娘怎么知道 Ted
I don't know how fucking big my finger is, Ted!
你只要像个男子汉
Just be a man,
站出来
stand up,
买他妈一个戒指 清楚没
get the fuckin' ring, all right?
好
Okay.
操 没搞错吧
You're fucking kidding.
女士 对不起 我无意听到了
Ma'am, I'm sorry. I couldn't help but overhear.
就是...你要结婚了
I just... you're getting married.
我想第一个恭喜你
I wanted to be the first one to offer my congratulations.
这样 Ken 嗯
Okay. Ken? - Yeah.
看我嘴型...不准读我唇语
Read my lips... Don't read my lips.
懂吗 嗯
you understand me? - Yeah.
好
Okay.
知道没 知道 好
you got it? - I got it. Okay.
我们走 走着
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Jim Palmer.
副总统女士 很高兴见到你 这邀请真是...
- Madam Vice President, nice to meet you. - What a treat...
欢迎来到卡姆登球场 谢谢
Welcome to Camden Yards. - Thank you.
Jim 你是名人堂成员 他们让我进去了
- So, Jim, you are a hall-of-famer. - They let me in there.
对啊 多好的事儿啊 进了...
Oh, yes, that is a wonderful thing to be in...
进了名人堂 各种好
in the hall of fame, for sure.
各种好 对
for Sure. - Yes.
好
Okay.
得合影了对吧
Okay, it's time for the group photo, right?
行 挺好的
All right, great.
大家一起说 金莺
Okay, everyone say Orioles.
金莺 非常好
- Orioles! - Great.
我们就到这儿吧 都合影了呢 是的
- Okay, I guess we're done. We got the shot. - Got it.
感谢大家的合作
Okay, everybody, thank you so much.
上帝保佑美国 谢谢
God bless America. - Thank you.
谢谢
Okay, thank you.
谢谢 不用谢
Thank you. - Okay.
副总统离开了体育场 20分钟会到这儿
Veep has left the stadium. She's gonna be here in 20.
真好
Okay.
最后想个节目来娱乐这些小朋友
One last push to keep these kids entertained.
我刚看到那里面有把吉他
You know, I saw a guitar in there.
你弹吉他 好吧
You play the guitar, all right?
这种情况我不弹
Not in this situation.
你可以的 Amy 不行
- Yes. Yes. - Amy, no.
哥弹吉他是为了泡妞 不是留住小朋友 知道吧
My guitar is for seduction, not crowd control, all right?
就算今晚月色不错 那也是一回事 老子不干
Granted, on a good night that's one and the same, but still.
不 老娘去找把吉他
No, we're finding you a guitar.
就做这个 噢 真可爱
- That's what we're doing. - Oh, isn't this cute?
你俩做了果汁 柠檬汁
Look At you Guys making juice. - Leon.
走开 你在这干嘛
Go away. Why are you here?
噢... 她其实在打招呼
Oh... - She means Hello.
实际上我有个段子要跟副总统讨论下
I actually have a story I'd like to discuss with the veep.
她到了没
She here yet?
没到 也是啊 她不爱准时
No. No, of course not, because she hates punctuality
也不爱善治
almost as much as good governance.
那我们接下来干嘛呢
So what should we do, guys?
没有 对不起 先生 现在我们对此事不予置评
No, I'm sorry, sir. We have no comment on that at the moment.
谢谢 再见
Thank you. Goodbye.
我们干嘛不准笑
Why would we need to ban smiling?
又不是说我们一有时间就会做这个
It's not like something we have time for in the first place.
女士 Sue 听着...
- Ma'am. - Sue, listen...
Ted六到八周前对我求婚了 知道吧
Ted proposed to me about six to eight weeks ago, okay?
噢 恭喜啊 女士
Oh, congratulations, ma'am.
不 不 他不是真求
No, no, no, he didn't really.
我们要假装他求了
We're just gonna pretend that he did.
那行 我一口咬定他做了
Okay. I assume he's in on this.
所以我现在要你
So now what I need you to do
帮我看看日历
is go to my calendar thing, please,
为那天选个日子
and let's find a date where this would have happened.
儿童勇气奖那天...他会求婚吗
The Children of Courage Awards... Would he have proposed then?
不行 那些小朋友有秃头症
No, no, uh-uh. That's kids with alopecia,
他们妈妈就是个神经...各种怪异
their mothers are on crack... that's a complete freak show.
好吧 啊 两个月前
Okay. Ah. Two months ago,
你和Ted去看冰球赛 还共进晚餐了
you and Ted went to an ice hockey game and had dinner after.
完美 就这个
Perfect. Yes.
好吗？ 感谢你
Okay? Thank you very much.
Sue Sue Sue 总统打了电话没
Sue, Sue, Sue, did the president call?
没 没 好吧
- No. - No. Yeah, okay. Right.
A和弦和E和弦是基本
The as and the es are like your basics.
弹蓝调什么的都要用的
That's like the roots of blues and stuff.
不过如果你...倾向于疯克乐什么的 (黑人爵士乐)
But if you really... if you get into some of the funkier stuff,
就得...看 找小七
that's the... see, it's the sevenths.
第七小调会给出一种...
It's the minor sevenths that give it that...
秋天的感觉...忧郁的感觉
sort of that autumn... that sort of gloom to it.
我很爱的
I just love that.
有点阴晴不定 有点催眠 但是我喜欢
It's kind of moody, sort of sleepy, but I like it.
这个...这个可以配合...
It's... it does well with the...
等你们长大了就知道了
You'll figure that out when you get older.
那...
So it's...
你们觉得好玩吗 不好玩
you having fun? - No.
听到没 不好玩 你真不好玩
Hear that? No fun. You are no fun.
副总统到了哦 耶
- The vice president is here. - Yay!
Leon West在这儿 噢 太好了
- Leon West is here. - Oh, great.
万事俱备 只欠我爸妈登上Skype了 (网络语音沟通工具)
Now all we need are my parents on Skype.
你买了验孕棒没
Do you have the tests?
买了一只 Gary会带更多过来
I have one. Gary's coming with more.
我们要验得越多次越好
We're gonna have more tests than you have pee.
你告诉Gary了?
You told Gary?
噢 你好 这样才能让他买验孕棒啊
- Oh, hello! - So he could get the tests.
好 真相只有一个 让Gary来做测试
Okay, we'll found out. I'll just have Gary do the tests.
那有效果吗 不 不是说用他的尿 Amy
- How will that work? - No, not with his pee, Amy.
嗨 等等
- Hi! - Wait a second.
所以...女士...你才是怀孕那个?
So... so, ma'am... so you're the one who's pregnant?
我是可能怀孕 所以我们会有场婚礼要办咯
- I might be pregnant. - So we're looking at a wedding.
或者自杀 我还没决定选哪个
Or a suicide. I haven't decided which.
看看这些小朋友多可爱
Look at these fantastic children!
副总统女士 你好 对不起我迟到了
- Madam Vice President. - Hello. I'm so sorry I'm late.
真的很抱歉
I have never meant those words more.
很高兴见到你
It's a pleasure to meet you.
孩子们准备好了 正在等你
The children are waiting and ready for you.
可以的话 我想
You know, I need to use
去下洗手间 很快
the ladies' room very briefly, if I may.
当然 厕所在那边
Of course. The staff restroom is right there.
太好了 我还有点口渴
Fantastic. I'm also parched
所以我在想...
and I'm wondering if I might...
能不能喝杯水 当然了
Can I have a cup of water? - of course.
纸杯子是最好的 好
Maybe in a paper Cup? - Yeah.
我们只有这种 给 噢 这是个...
- This is all we have. Here. - Oh! Well, this is...
这是个塑料的... 应该没关系
- Okay, it's in a plastic, clear... - It should be fine.
没关系哦 没关系
- It'll be fine. - It'll be fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
别拍了
Okay, cool it.
噢 我的天
Oh, good lord.
你怎么想的 她真怀孕了?
So what do you think? Is she really pregnant?
我怎么知道
How should I know?
你是女人啊 什么
- You're a woman. - What?
你觉得当女人就可以连
You think that as a woman I might sense some disturbance
别人子宫里的情况都感应了
in the fuckin' lady matrix?
嘿 Ken 还好吧 挺好的
- Hey, Ken. How's it going? - Good.
嘿 跟金莺队照相的时候我没在
Hey, I missed that photo with the Orioles.
你可以魔术般地把我P进去么
Do you think you can kind of do your magic and photoshop me into it?
技术上是可以的 哦 真好
- Technically, yes. - Oh, okay.
道德上是不行的
Ethically, no.
我只提供事实 从不捏造
I document. I don't invent.
你自己P
Do it yourself.
好吧 你手好热哦
Okay. You got hot hands.
嘿 她跟孩子们唱了歌没
Hey, did she sing with the kids yet?
还没 没
Not yet. - No.
太好了 她在哪呢
Awesome. Where is she?
厕所 这样
bathroom. - Okay.
他妈的 Leon West也来了?
Holy shitballs. Leon West is here?
对啊 我以为你知道的
Uh-huh. I thought you knew that.
这哥们就像钙片...哪儿都有 (男同色情片)
The guy's like gay porn... He's everywhere.
他们只有
Okay, okay, they only had
三种验孕棒
three types of pregnancy tests I could find.
嗨 Gary 没关系 有这么多了
Hi, Gary. Okay, that's okay. We have plenty.
她在厕所 我们干嘛要现在搞这个
- She's in the bathroom. - Why are we doing this now?
因为你说怀孕的事已经流传出去了
Because you said that the pregnancy story is out there,
所以我们要现在确认啊
so we need to make sure right now.
嘿 Mike 嗨 女士
- Hey, Mike. - Hi, ma'am.
我没说你怀孕的事传出去了
I never said the pregnancy story's out there.
你说了 就在电话里说的
Yes. On the phone you said the press
媒体说她怀孕了
is saying that she's pregnant.
我说她讨厌 我说Selina很讨厌
I said she's repugnant. I said Selina's repugnant.
什么 为什么我被讨厌
What? Why am I repugnant?
Leon是因为
Leon said it in reference
你炒了那特勤人员才说的
to you firing the secret service agent.
就是在背后笑那事? 对
The smile story? - Yeah.
这事为什么会传出去呢 Mike
Why is that story out there now, Mike?
我不知道
I don't know.
对 我不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
真的假的
Really?
女士 我们真要讨论这个...
Ma'am, if we just table this...
也得先把孩子们的事给解决了
I think we should just knock off the kid thing.
放低点 我们先搞定这个
Lower that. - We need to Get this over with.
我们准备好了 要见孩子了好兴奋的
You know, I think we're ready. Very excited for the kids.
给 你来做测试 噢
- Here, can you test this? - Oh!
嗨 噢 Leon
Hi! Oh, Leon!
此时此刻能跟你握手真开心
So pleased to be shaking your hand right at this moment.
见到你也很开心 = 真开心
- It's wonderful to see you, too. - Just delighted.
你见过Ken没 Ken 我们上
Have you met Ken? Ken, let's get moving.
这边走
Right this way.
对不起 我迟到了一点
Well, I'm so sorry I was a little bit late,
不过我要跟一群无聊的大人打交道
but I had to hang out with a bunch of boring grown-ups.
- Bugh. Boo! - Boo!
Boo!
Saunders夫人
Mrs. Saunders,
我听说孩子们
I understand that the boys and girls
准备了一首歌
have a song that they wanna sing.
好 小朋友们 数四声唱
Okay, kids. Now, after four.
知道吗 1 2 3 4
All right? One, two, three, four.
嘿 老爸 等着看照片吧
Hey, dad. Just wait until you see the photo.
超棒的
It's awesome.
没错 我就是干了爷们的活
You're right, I do do a proper man's job.
噢 天呐
Oh, God.
您真的怀了个孕呢
You're very, very pregnant.
噢 哇 唱得太好了 是不是很好?
Oh, wow! That was marvelous. Wasn't that great?
今天真有趣 谢谢... 是不是很好?
- Fun day. Thank you so... - Wasn't it great?
对 真是好歌
Yes, what a good song.
我们要赶下一个议程了
We're gonna have to go on to the next thing.
噢 太不凑巧了
- Oh, darn it. - I know.
我们要走了 真遗憾
We have to leave. What a shame.
我想一整天都在这儿
I wish I could be here all day.
做得好 好了 做得好
- Good job. - Okay, good job.
太棒了 各位拜拜
Wonderful. Bye-bye, everybody.
拜 拜
- Bye! - Bye.
拜拜 以后见
Bye-bye. See you later.
不要碰我
Don't touch.
就这样? 孩子们 什么感觉?
That's it? How about that, kids?
等了一天呢
Waited all day for that.